Guide to the Jim Dow photographs, 1966-2019 RL.11709
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jim Dow photographs
1966-2019
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Dow, Jim, 1942-
RL.11709
98.5 Linear Feet 118 boxes
10 Terabytes 2 hard drives (HDD)
Jim Dow (1942- ) is an American photographer based in Massachusetts. The core of the collection consists of approximately 1905 black-and-white and color sheet negatives, representing images taken by Dow from 1966 to 2018. These are accompanied by a large set of teaching slides and electronic files for his art and photography courses. Dow's photographs feature 20th century U.S. vernacular architecture and landscapes in New England, the U.S. West, Midwest, and the South, with a focus on North Dakota and Massachusetts; multi-panel panoramas of sports stadiums and athletic fields, chiefly in the U.S. and U.K.; and the architecture and interiors of private clubs, libraries, and large public buildings such as churches and museums in cities around the world. Also featured is a series on food trucks and taco trucks, chiefly in the U.S. and Mexico. Other important travel images were taken in Argentina and Uruguay. Regardless of location, many of Dow's photographs include outdoor advertising and cultural expressions such as murals, handpainted signs, bar decor, and graffiti; people are rarely present. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
The majority of the negative sheets measure 8x10 inches, with the remainder measuring 4x5 inches.
Arrangement
Arranged in three series: Negatives; Teaching Slides; and Teaching Files (electronic format). The negatives are arranged in rough chronological sequence and by bodies of work. Within these groups, the negatives are organized by the photographer's original identifiers.
Conditions Governing Access
Film negatives (first series) are closed to research. Please contact the Rubenstein Library for more information.
Conditions Governing Access
The electronic files are in process and are currently closed to use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Jim Dow photographs were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 2019 and 2020.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
All negatives were developed on safety film. The majority are in color; black-and-white negatives bear the earliest dates.
Scope and Contents
The core of the collection consists of approximately 1905 black-and-white and color film negatives by photographer Jim Dow, representing images taken from 1966 to 2018. The images document Dow's extensive travels chiefly in Argentina, Uruguay, England, Mexico, across much of the United States, and to a lesser extent in Canada, Portugal and Scotland. The great majority of the photographs were shot with an 8x10 inch view camera and color film; the black-and-white negatives typically measure 4x5 inches and represent Dow's earliest work.
Dow is best known for his studies of U.S. 20th century vernacular architecture and landscapes in New England, the U.S. West, the Midwest, and Southern States; for his multi-panel panoramas of baseball, football, and soccer stadiums and athletic fields, chiefly in the U.S. and U.K.; and for his images of the architecture and interiors of private clubs, libraries, and large public buildings such as churches, museums, and civic buildings in cities around the world.
The earliest photographs in the collection were taken in almost every region of the lower 48 states, beginning in 1966 and continuing through 2018. Starting out in black-and-white then soon transitioning to color, they document small towns and roadside attractions, well-worn business façades, and gathering places such as barbequeue joints, bars, event halls, and diners. North Dakota features prominently, as do California, Louisiana, Massachusetts, North Carolina, Pennsylvania, Texas, Virginia, and Wyoming. There is also a series on food trucks and taco trucks in the U.S., Mexico, and South America. Regardless of location, many of Dow's photographs include details of outdoor advertising and cultural expressions such as murals, handpainted signs, bar decor, and graffiti; people are rarely present.
Also included are photographs representing Dow's commissioned work (1985-2008), chiefly taken at New England universities and private schools such as MIT, Yale, Tufts, Vassar, and Phillips Academy.
Accompanying the negatives archive is a large set of approximately 120,960 teaching slides and hundreds of electronic files related to Dow's photography and art courses, dating from approximately 1980 to 2019.
These materials form the first two installments of the photographer's archive at Duke University. Additions of photographic prints and professional papers are anticipated.
Advertising, Outdoor -- Photographs; Architecture -- Photographs; Baseball fields -- Photographs; Documentary Photography -- United States; Folk art -- Photographs; Food trucks -- Photographs; Outdoor art -- Photographs; Photographers -- United States; Photography -- History; Photography -- Study and teaching; Private clubs -- United States -- Photographs; Soccer fields -- Photographs; Stadiums -- Photographs; Vernacular architecture -- Photographs; Argentina -- Photographs; Boston (Mass.) -- Photographs; England -- Photographs; England -- Social life and customs -- 20th century; London (England) -- Photographs; Massachusetts -- Photographs; Mexico -- Photographs; New England -- Photographs; North Dakota -- Photographs; Southern States -- Photographs; United States -- Photographs; United States -- Social life and customs -- 20th century; Uruguay -- Photographs; West (U.S.) -- Photographs; Black-and-white negatives; Color negatives; Digital images; Electronic records; Negatives (photographs); Slides (photographs); Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Dow, Jim, 1942-
- Negatives, 1966-2018; Original identifiers generally consist of the year taken and a two-digit number; after the 1970s the photographer's initials (jdd) preface all identifiers but are not expressed in this inventory. A few of the earliest identifiers may not always include the year, but others have been standardized to this system. Because the negatives represent a selection from the total career output, there are frequent gaps in numbering.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Negatives are closed to research. Please contact the Rubenstein Library for more information.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  A duplicate set of negatives is held by the photographer.
  - U.S. Road, 1966 April-November; 1 folder (Box 1)
    General
    Legacy identifiers: [1966-]05 to 056
    Scope and Contents
    Locations include: Roxbury, Belmont, Boston, Clinton, Revere, Cape Cod, MA; Pungoteague, VA. Black-and-white 4x5 inch negatives.
  - U.S. Road, 1966-1968; 1 folder (Box 1)
    Legacy identifiers: 01 to 20, 42 to 92
    Locations include: Belmont, Boston, and other locations in Eastern MA; various places in VA. Black-and-white 4x5 inch negatives.
  - U.S. Road, 1967 February-December; 1 folder (Box 1)
    Legacy identifiers: [1967-]02 to 36
    Locations include: Fall River, Belmont, and Chelsea, MA; Fredericksburg and Keeling, VA; Bristol, RI; Beaufort, SC; New Bern and Edenton, NC; Vancouver, Quebec; New Hampshire; Selma, AL. Black-and-white 4x5 inch negatives.
  - U.S. Road, 1968 January-August; 1 folder (Box 1)
    Legacy identifiers: [1968-]01 to 64
    Locations include: Lynn, MA; Cincinnati, OH; Georgia; Alabama; Kentucky; Florida; South Carolina; Easton and Bethlehem, PA; Arkansas; Bonham, Ivanhoe and Hodges, TX; Yadkin, N.C.; South Boston, Danville, VA; Rhode Island; New Brunswick; Nova Scotia. Black-and-white 4x5 inch negatives.
  - U.S. Road, 1969 January-December; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Legacy identifiers: none
    Locations include: Uxbridge and Belmont, MA; Quebec; Chesapeake and Danville, VA; Ballouville, CT; Bronx, N.Y. Many of these photographs are portraits of people. Both 4x5 and 8x10 inch sizes. Large sizes appear to be reprints of 1969 4x5 inch negatives. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1970; 4 folders (Box 2)
    Legacy identifiers: 1970-01 to 1970-032C; some are only identified by year
    4x5 inch negatives locations include: Decatur, AL; Belmont, MA; Blairgowrie, Portree, Glasgow, Scotland; 8x10 inch locations include: Pulaski, TN; New Orleans, LA; Portageville, MO; Belmont, Sumerville, Westport, Fairhaven, Berlin, Clinton, Webster, Everett, MA; Woonsocket, RI; Ballouville, Manchester, CT; Geneva, Little Falls, NY. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1971; 1 folder (Box 2)
    Locations include: New Haven, CT; Cambridge, Brookline, Belmont, Lynn, Leominster, Brockton, Boston, MA; Ironton, Higginsport, OH; South Bend, Danville, Ingram, VA. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1971; 1 folder (Box 3)
    Legacy identifiers: only date and year
    Locations include: Martinsville, VA; Eden, NC; Williamsport, MD; Belmont, Wilmington, Quincy, Boston, MA; Baldwinsville, NY; Branford, CT; Grenada, MS; Pt. Marion, PA; Cornelia, GA. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1972; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Locations include: Boston, Revere Beach, and Belmont, MA; Greensburg, Carbondale, and Coatesville, PA; Atlantic City, Liden, and Hightstown, NJ; Saugerties and Sharon, NY; Canton, Springfield, and Sydney, OH; Anita, IA; Shoshoni, WY; Brandy, NE; Big Timber, Hardin, and Billings, MT; Mantako, MN; Pittsfield, NH. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1973; 5 folders (Box 4)
    Legacy identifiers: 1973-01 to 1973-106
    Locations include: Savannah, Sparta, Carrollton, and Atlanta, GA; Bolivar, Pulaski, Waynesboro, Cleveland, Cookeville, Knoxville, and Norristown, TN; Madison, Memphis, Benton, Hot Springs, Conway, Elidg, Eureka Springs, Desha, Searey, Vanndale, and Corning, AK; Bent, Grants, Gallup, Clovis, LaLonde, and Albuquerque, NM; Aguila, Quartzite, Kingman, and Valentine, AZ; Los Angeles, Long Beach, Duarte, Alhambra, North Hollywood, Santa Monica, and Bartow, CA; Seymour and Dickens, TX; Wynnewood, OK; Webb City, Cabool, Mountainview, Greenfield, Willow Springs, and Freeburg, MO; Orangeburg, SC; Dayton, and Xenia, OH; Mount Hope and Wichita, KS; Marienville, IL; Parkersburg, Wolf Summit, Grafton, Powers, and Wheeling, WV; Philadelphia, The Bronx, Rhinebeck, Saratoga Springs, Loudonville, Whitney Point, Corning, and Chemung, NY; Conway, Martha's Vineyard, Dartmouth, Belmont, Danvers, Blairsville, and Shelburne, MA; Pittston, Elizabeth, Millersburg, Carbon, and Shamokin, PA; Huntington, VA; Whitenburg, Neon, KY; Stanford, CT. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1975; 1 folder (Box 4)
    Legacy identifiers: JSG-1 to JSG-32
    Locations include: Phillipsburg, NJ; Shenandoah and Chilhowie, VA; White Sulphur Springs, WV; Four Mile, KY; Elgin, Woodbury, Murfreesboro, and Persons, TN; Wabbaseka and Hot Springs, AK; Erick, OK; Greenwood and Bossier City, LA; Atlanta, Bay City, Beaumont, Blessing, Brownsville, Laredon, Eagle Pass, Del Rio, Martha and El Paso, TX. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1975; 4 folders (Box 5)
    Legacy identifiers: JSG-34 to JSG-176
    Locations include: El Paso, Canutillo, Brody, Fredericksburg, Austin, Bastrop, Orange, Beaumont, Longview, Gladewater, Dallas, Arlington, Houston, Seguin, Junction, Sonora, Sheffield, Balmorhea, TX; Hatch, Carizzon, Rockwell, Artesia, Hobbs, Santa Fe, Albuquerque, NM; Carbazon, Covina, Sherman Oaks, West Hollywood, Los Angeles, San Diego, El Centro, Julian, Azusa, Crowley, New Iberia, Bakersfield, Tarzana, Oxnard, Selma, Delhi, Sacramento, CA; Lafayette, New Orleans, Burnside, Lobdell, Waterproof, Cutoff, LA; Biloxi, MS; Albany, GA; Myrtle Beach, SC; Jacksonville, NC; Ocean City, MD; Auburn, Syracuse, New York, NY; Belmont, Boston, MA; Bangor, Orono, Fairfield, ME; Huntington, Johnsontown, Thompson, PA; Sussex, NJ; Martin's Ferry, Bridgeport, Columbus, Springfield, OH; Frankfort, Glasgow, Owensboro, KY; Parsons, Shiloh Battlefield, TN; Spring Dale, Eureka Springs, AK; Duniphan, MO; Sun City, AZ; Echo, OR. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1975; 2 folders (Box 6)
    Legacy identifiers: JSG-176 to JSG-240; 1975-70; and "JDD-88 or 89 or 90"
    Locations include: Pendleton, OR; Payette, Burley, and Pocatello, ID; Butte and Floweree, MT; Peru, IL; Elkhart, East Chicago, and Angola, IN; Euphoria, VA; Jesup and Griffin, GA; Fernandina Beach, Jacksonville Beach, Saint Augustine, Marineland, Smyrna Beach, Fort Pierce, Stuart, Margate, Boca Raton, Miami, Pahokee, Plant City, Palm Beach, Ellenton, and Bonifay, FL; Biloxi, MS; Bangor, ME. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1976; 4 folders (Box 6)
    Legacy identifiers: JSG-224 to JSG-257
    Locations include: Lake Placid and Miami, FL; White House and Princeton, NJ; Whitsett, Highpoint, and Micaville, NC; Biloxi, MS; El Centro, Calimesa, and Salida, CA; Theba, Gila Bend, and Phoenix, AZ; Las Animas and Lamar, CO; Blue Ridge, GA. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1977; 2 folders (Box 6)
    Legacy identifiers: 1977-266; 1977-267 to 1977-274; 1977-215 to 1977-252
    Locations include: Grand Prairie, Breckinridge, Milano, Jasper, Dallas, Lockhart, Cleveland, Waxahatchee, and Rosenberg, TX; Hammond, New Orleans, and Ruston, LA; Number Nine, AK; Fairview, KY; Gwynedd and Bethlehem, PA; Buena Vista, Martinsville, Vansant, Pennington, Danville, and Hillsville, VA; Jasper, TN; Bossier City, IA; St. Mary, WV; Old Town, ME; DeQueen, AK; Bennington, and Durant, OK. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1978; 2 folders (Box 6)
    Legacy identifiers: 1978-255 to 1978-322
    Locations include: Hot Springs, AK; Mt. Airy, NC; Medford and Newton, MA; Newtown, PA; Atlanta, Cedartown and Powder Springs, GA; Leeville, LaRose, New Orleans, Metairie, La Place, Cutoff, Napoleonville, Galliano, Donaldsonville, Thibodaux, Luling, and Bridge City, LA; Sheffield, Fairfax, and Seminole, AL; Chattanooga, TN; Pascagoula, Natchez, and Columbia, MS. Black-and-white and color.
  - U.S. Road, 1979; 2 folders (Box 6)
    Legacy identifiers: 1979-325 to 1979-404
    Locations include: Metairie, New Orleans, Sunset, Norco, Baton Rouge, and Shreveport, LA; Dallas, Austin, Henderson, Colorado City, Denton, Henderson, and Waskom, TX; Atlanta and Hapeville, GA; Meridian, MS; Russellville and Hot Springs, AK; Chandler, El Reno, and Thackerville, OK; Albuquerque, San Acacia, Consequences, and Deming, NM; Bristol, TN; Arlington, Cambridge, and Watertown, MA; Whitehouse and Westville, NJ; Newton, Bethlehem, Allentown and Dublin, PA. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1980; 1 folder (Box 7)
    Legacy identifiers: 1980-405 to 1980-447
    Locations include: Milton, MA; Central City, PA; Bellaire and Liverpool, OH; St. Charles and Bardstown, KY; Fair Dealing, MO; Essex, MS; Clayton and Las Vegas, NM; Bowie, AZ; Van Horn, Peco, Austin and Dallas, TX; Forest Hills, Dulay, Galliano, New Orleans and Pulaski, LA; Knoxville, TN; Wytheville and Roanoke, VA. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1981; 1 folder (Box 7)
    Legacy identifiers: 1981-618 to 1981-792
    Locations include: Toronto, Ontario, Canada; Madison, WI; Mitchell and Armour, SD; Gibbon, NE; Colorado Springs and Pueblo, CO; Wichita, Dallas, and Mesquite, TX; Bossier City, LA; Charleston, SC; London. Black-and-white.
  - U.S. Road, 1983; 2 folders (Box 7)
    Legacy identifiers: 1983-984 to 1983-992
    Locations include: Cincinnati and Hamilton, OH; Erlanger, Newport, and Covington, KY. Black-and-white.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 1980; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Legacy identifiers: 1980-450 to 1980-490; the rest by year
    Locations include: Leeds; West Ham, London, Arsenal, London; Chelsea, London; Sunderland. Color.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 1981; 5 folders (Box 8)
    Legacy identifiers: 1981-752 to 1981-793; 1981-1080
    Locations include: Leeds; Nottingham; Carlysle; Liverpool; Fulham, Tottenham and Islington, London; Aldershot; Glasgow and Edinburgh, Scotland. There is also one 3-piece panorama of IBROX Stadium in Glasgow and one of Wimbledon Tennis Stadium. Color.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 1983; 4 folders (Box 8)
    Locations include: Lord's Cricket Ground, London (5-panel); Nottingham (3-panel); Watford (3-panel); Manchester United in Old Trafford (2 4-panels); Twickenham Rugby Ground, London (3-panel). Color.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 1984; 12 folders (Box 8)
    Legacy identifiers: 1984-1087, 1984-1103; many more unnumbered
    Locations include: Luton; Wimbledon; Wembley; Arsenal; Huddersfield, N. Color. Yorkshire; Glasgow; Liverpool; Hendon; Tottenham; West Ham. Many of these are multi-panel panoramas. Color.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 1985; 9 folders (Box 8)
    Legacy identifiers: 1985-1120 to 1985-1162
    Locations include: West Ham; Highbury; St. Color. John's Wood; New Cross; Liverpool; London. Many of these are multi-panel panoramas. Color.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 1986; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Legacy identifier: 1986-1201
    Locations include: West Ham; Upton Park. Color.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 1993; 1 folder (Box 8)
    5 panel panorama, Hillsborough Stadium, Sheffield Wednesday. Color.
  - U.K. Stadiums, 2016; 1 folder (Box 8)
    Legacy identifiers: 2016-08 to 2016-22
    Location: West Ham. Many of these are multi-panel panoramas. Color.
  - North Dakota, 1981; 4 folders (Box 9)
    Legacy identifiers: 1981-508 to 1981-704.
    Locations include: Auburn; Gato; Grafton; Casselton; Grand Forks; Hatton; Cashel; Carrington; Minot; Wabek; New Town; Marshall; Parshall; Raub; Sweet Briar; New Salem; Bismarck; Ft. Yates; Shields; Jamestown; Fargo; Kathryn; Hague; Mandan; Hebron; Golva; Marmarth; Rhame; Bowman; Amidon; Dickenson; Gladstone; Belfield; Tioga; Kenmare; Cando; Cathay; Strasbury; Linton; Mott; Belfield; Pingree; Leeds; Michigan; Velva, all in ND; also Aberdeen, Wolsey, SD; Kearney, NE. Color.
  - Clubs, 2002; 5 folder (Box 10)
    Legacy identifiers: 2002-01 to 2002-145. Early formats take the form: #02-01.
    Location: New York. Color.
  - Clubs, 2003; 1 folder (Box 10)
    Legacy identifiers: 2002-02 to 2002-08
  - U.S. Road, 2002; 1 folder (Box 11)
    Legacy identifiers: 2002-050 to 2002-091
    BBQ; Locations include: Albany, NY; Kansas City, MO; Somerville, MA. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2004; 2 folders (Box 11)
    Legacy identifiers: 2004-122 to 2004-153
    BBQ; New Market, Harrisonburg, Staunton, Lynchburg, Stony Creek, and Richmond, VA; Burlington, Hillsborough, Foxborough, Durham, Chapel Hill, Illington, Fayetteville, Denn, Goldsboro, Dudley, Mt. Olive, Calypso, Kenansville, Pink Hill, Kinston, and Rocky Mount, NC. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2007; 1 folder (Box 11)
    Legacy identifiers: 2007-82 to 2007-83
    BBQ; Location: Midland, MI. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2009; 1 folder (Box 11)
    Legacy identifiers: 2009-03 to 2009-124
    BBQ; Locations include: Los Angeles, CA; Grand Isle, Houma, Raceland, Golden Meadow, Raceland, La Fourche Parish, Allemands, Paradis, Des Allemands, and La Rose, LA. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2010; 1 folder (Box 11)
    Legacy identifiers: 2010-000 to 2010-15
    BBQ; Locations include: Durham, NC; McClellanville, SC. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2011; 3 folders (Box 11)
    Legacy identifiers: 2011-01 to 2011-136
    BBQ; Locations include: Paradis, Baton Rouge, New Orleans, Franklin, Baldwin, New Iberia, Rayne, Elton, Krotz Springs, and Kenner, LA; Vicksburg, Greenville, MS; Riverside, and Rio Vista, CA; Beaumont and Nederland, TX; Holly Hill and Hemingway, SC; Chapel Hill, NC. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1981; 10 folders (Box 12)
    Legacy identifiers: 1981-630 to 1981-747; ML 708-1981
    Locations include: Asheville, Greensboro, and Durham, NC; Madison, WI; Denver, CO; Lubbock and Dallas, TX; Birmingham, AL. Many of these are multi-panel panoramas. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1984; 2 folders (Box 12)
    Legacy identifiers: 1984-1063 to 1984-1077
    Locations include: Bluefield, WV; Bristol, Elizabethton, Knoxville, and Nashville TN; Asheville, NC; Jackson, MS; Shreveport, LA; Little Rock, AK. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1987; 12 folders (Box 12)
    Legacy identifiers: 1987-1270 to 1987-1338
    Locations include: Pulaski, Salem, and Hampton, VA; Johnson, TN; Asheville, Gastonia, and Burlington, NC; Spartanburg, SC; Buffalo and Rochester, NY. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1988; 24 folders (Box 12)
    Legacy identifiers: 1988-1341 to 1988-1366
    Locations include: Hagerstown, MD; Reading, PA; Elmira, Geneva, Auburn, Batavia, Oneonta, and Jamestown, NY; Britain, CT; Pittsfield, MA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League Baseball, Non-Portfolio, 1981; 7 folders (Box 13)
    Legacy identifiers: 1981-627 to 1981-739
    Locations include: Chicago, IL; Detroit, MI; Bloomington, MN; Atlanta, GA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League Baseball, Non-Portfolio, 1982; 42 folders (Box 13)
    Legacy identifiers: 1982-803 to 1982-885
    Locations include: Boston, MA; Queens, NY; Pittsburg, PA; Cleveland and Cincinnati, OH; Detroit, MI; Chicago, IL; Milwaukee, WI; Bloomington, MN; Seattle, WA; Oakland, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Anaheim, and San Diego, CA; Kansas City and St. Louis, MO; Baltimore, MD; Houston, TX; Atlanta, GA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League and others, 1982; 1 folder (Box 14)
    Legacy identifiers: 1982-883
    Location: Atlanta, Georgia. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League and others, 1988; 7 folders (Box 14)
    Legacy identifiers: 1988-1368 to 1988-1374
    Locations include: Buffalo, NY; Clinton, Davenport, IA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League and others, 1990; 3 folders (Box 14)
    Legacy identifiers: 1990-1640 to 1990-1642
    Location: Chicago, IL. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League and others, 1992; 5 folders (Box 14)
    Legacy identifiers: 1992-1826 to 1992-1946
    Locations include: Baltimore, MD; New York, NY. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League and others, 1995; 1 folder (Box 14)
    Location: Denver, CO. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Major League Baseball: Portfolio, Approximately 1980-1982; 26 folders (Box 15)
    Legacy identifiers: none, identification by date and year.
    Locations include: Philadelphia and Pittsburgh, PA; Chicago, IL; Boston, MA; Bronx, NY; Arlington and Houston, TX; Cleveland, OH; Detroit, MI; Atlanta, GA; Milwaukee, WI; Minneapolis, MN; Seattle, WA; Oakland, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Anaheim, and San Diego, CA; Kansas City and St. Louis, MO; Montreal, Canada. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Non-Baseball, 1981; 8 folders (Box 16)
    Legacy identifiers: 1981-618; ML 1981-622 to ML 1981-740
    Locations include: Toronto, Ontario (Canada); Pontiac, MI; Chicago, IL; Bloomington, MN; Colorado Springs, CO; Irving, TX; Baton Rouge, LA; Atlanta, GA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Non-Baseball, 1984; 17 folders (Box 16)
    Legacy identifiers: 1984-993 to 1984-1032
    Locations include: Westwood, Los Angeles; Los Angeles, Arcadia, Inglewood, Long Beach, Pasadena, and Malibu, CA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Non-Baseball, 1985; 2 folders (Box 16)
    Legacy identifiers: 1985-1171, 1985-1172
    Locations: Grand Forks, ND; The Meadowlands, NJ. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Non-Baseball, 1986; 1 folder (Box 16)
    Legacy identifiers: 1986-1183
    Location: St. Color. Louis, MO. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Non-Baseball, 1993; 8 folders (Box 16)
    Legacy identifiers: 1993-1916 to 1993-1952; some with no identifiers
    Locations include: New Haven, CT; Washington, D. C.; Chicago, IL; Palo Alto, San Jose, CA; Dallas, TX. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Non-Baseball, 1994; 12 folders (Box 16)
    Legacy identifiers: 1994-1011 to 1994-1062
    Locations include: Los Angeles, Westwood, Dominguez Hills, and Carson, CA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Non-Baseball, 1996; 2 folders (Box 16)
    Legacy identifiers: 1996-46 a-c
    Location: Princeton, NJ. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1983; 60 folders (Box 17)
    Legacy identifiers: 889-967